<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-02-23T16:49:43+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">find Chinese products and manufacturers</title><subtitle>find valuable Chinese products and manufacturers</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Redmi K20 Pro won the first in Chinese 618 Shopping Festival</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/redmi-k20-pro-won-the-first-in-chinese-618-shopping-festival" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Redmi K20 Pro won the first in Chinese 618 Shopping Festival" /><published>2019-06-03T03:55:00+08:00</published><updated>2019-06-03T03:55:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/redmi-k20-pro-won-the-first-in-chinese-618-shopping-festival</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/redmi-k20-pro-won-the-first-in-chinese-618-shopping-festival"><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Yesterday was the first day of JD.com 618
Shopping Festival. A number of popular new smartphones, including Redmi K20
Pro, went on sale yesterday. Today, JD announced the ranking of mobile phone
sales on June 1. Redmi K20 Pro won the championship of mobile phone sales, as
well as the championship of new mobile phone sales, ranking first in the price between
2000 and 3000.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:image {"id":39} -->
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="http://valuefinding.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/06/timg.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-39" /></figure>
<!-- /wp:image -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Redmi in the middle and low end of the
market share is quite large, then why do you have to do something about
flagship smartphone? This is the question that Lu Weibing, vice president of
Xiaomi Group and general manager of the Redmi brand, is often asked, especially
after the independence of the REDMI brand this year.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>On May 28, Redmi officially launched two
new flagship products, Redmi K20 and Redmi K20 Pro, while updating the low-end
product line to Redmi 7A. So far, Redmi has formed a complete product system of
"high-quality and extreme performance" on the smartphone, which has
realized the transformation from red rice to Redmi. Redmi forms the layout of
the whole product line.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>In fact, REDMI set a strategy early on:
adhere to the ultimate value for money, adhere to high quality, speed up
internationalization, prepare for the high-end market. The Redmi K20 series is
REDMI's first performance flagship smartphone. After independence from Xiaomi,
the Redmi brand took only 4 months to complete the full product layout from the
high quality Volkswagen to the ultimate performance flagship. </p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content><author><name>huujuun</name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Yesterday was the first day of JD.com 618 Shopping Festival. A number of popular new smartphones, including Redmi K20 Pro, went on sale yesterday. Today, JD announced the ranking of mobile phone sales on June 1. Redmi K20 Pro won the championship of mobile phone sales, as well as the championship of new mobile phone sales, ranking first in the price between 2000 and 3000.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Realme returned to the Chinese market with the aim of besieging Xiaomi and REDMI</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/realme-returned-to-the-chinese-market-with-the-aim-of-besieging-xiaomi-and-redmi" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Realme returned to the Chinese market with the aim of besieging Xiaomi and REDMI" /><published>2019-05-31T02:29:00+08:00</published><updated>2019-05-31T02:29:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/realme-returned-to-the-chinese-market-with-the-aim-of-besieging-xiaomi-and-redmi</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/realme-returned-to-the-chinese-market-with-the-aim-of-besieging-xiaomi-and-redmi"><![CDATA[<!-- wp:image {"id":31} -->
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="http://valuefinding.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/5ce3a41cc5198-thumb.png" alt="" class="wp-image-31" /></figure>
<!-- /wp:image -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>A few days ago, two pictures were circulated on the Internet. Once again, the competition in the Chinese smartphone market is fierce. Among them, Xiaomi has once again become the target of public criticism. One of them is so-called “two vs dozens”. including 10 Chinese mobile phone brands including Huawei, Honor, OPPO, and vivo, and Xiaomi, it seems that Xiaomi is  besieged by other Chinese mobile phone brands including Huawei, Honor, OPPO, Realme and ViVO,  As for  Huawei and Honor, it is quite like a sense of sitting aside and watching the battle. It is said that OPPO returned to the Chinese market with the aim of besieging Redmi and Xiaomi.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Among a crowd of Chinese mobile phone manufacturers, due to Oppo and Vivo's previous success in entertainment marketing and sales channels, so that Oppo and Vivo with a certain sales base, is considered is the most innovative to challenge Huawei.  Last year OPPO Find X and Vivo  NEX were thought to be successful to rely on innovation to build high-end handsets and get good sales, but from last year's performance across the Chinese market, the facts are far from as simple as we've seen.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>In fact, although the picture appears to be
these Chinese mobile phone manufacturers in competition with Xiaomi, but from
the current market reality, because Huawei (including Honor) in the Chinese
market has been a big lead, Xiaomi has basically made it difficult to pose a
substantial threat. As early as last year, Honor has declared that Xiaomi is
not an opponent. As for other Chinese mobile phone manufacturers, in addition
to Oppo and Vivo, other so-called Xiaomi's Chinese mobile phone manufacturers
are nothing more than a bunch of "catch", it is difficult to let
Xiaomi bruise, especially with cost-effective play. So all that's left is Oppo
and Vivo, and from last year to this year Oppo and Vivo’s performance and
changes in the Chinese market, Xiaomi is, in a way, the biggest opponent of Oppo
and Vivo now and in the future.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content><author><name>huujuun</name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Realme officially detached from OPPO, will it be the next oneplus?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/realme-officially-detached-from-oppo-will-it-be-the-next-one-plus" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Realme officially detached from OPPO, will it be the next oneplus?" /><published>2019-05-30T14:18:00+08:00</published><updated>2019-05-30T14:18:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/realme-officially-detached-from-oppo-will-it-be-the-next-one-plus</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/realme-officially-detached-from-oppo-will-it-be-the-next-one-plus"><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p> OPPO is on the list of  top four Chinese smartphone brands which is called "HMOV" . On May 1, OPPO officially announced the launch of its mobile phone sub-brand, Realme. In India ,Realme share the OPPO production line for manufacturing, and two weeks later launched the brand's first phone--Realme 1.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>In less than 3 months, the OPPO, a
sub-brand fighting redmi in the Indian market, has achieved remarkable results,
with Realme 1 selling 400,000 units and taking a 1% share of India's smartphone
market, according to research agency CounterPoint</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>And almost as much as most mobile phone
sub-brands, Realme's fate eventually broke away from the parent company and
operated independently.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Li Bingzhong, the former vice president of
OPPO and head of OPPO overseas marketing, officially announced on Twitter that
he would serve as Realme's CEO and operate the Realme brand, which focus on overseas
markets, in the hope of providing young people around the world products with
design trends and strong performance.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>After the official announcement on Twitter,
OPPO CEO Chen Mingyong also forwarded Twitter, and blessed:</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Set out with enthusiasm, , bless the brand
realme!</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>At this point, Realme took less than 3
months from birth, to launching the first product, to operating independently
from OPPO. According to Phoenix Science and Technology reported that the Realme
brand behind the operating company for Shenzhen Realme Mobile Communications
Co., Ltd., its registration on June 1, 2018, Li Bingzhong as a corporate
company, registered capital of 50 million yuan, by the company of OPPO CEO Chen
Mingyong as general manager of Guangdong Ou Jia Communications Technology Co.,
Ltd. 100% shareholding.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content><author><name>huujuun</name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[OPPO is on the list of top four Chinese smartphone brands which is called "HMOV" . On May 1, OPPO officially announced the launch of its mobile phone sub-brand, Realme. In India ,Realme share the OPPO production line for manufacturing, and two weeks later launched the brand's first phone--Realme 1.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Interview with Founder and CEO of Huawei Ren Zhengfei’s in Shenzhen, China, Question 8</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/founder-and-ceo-of-huawei-ren-zhengfeis-interview-in-shenzhen-china-question-8" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Interview with Founder and CEO of Huawei Ren Zhengfei’s in Shenzhen, China, Question 8" /><published>2019-05-29T07:22:00+08:00</published><updated>2019-05-29T07:22:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/founder-and-ceo-of-huawei-ren-zhengfeis-interview-in-shenzhen-china-question-8</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/founder-and-ceo-of-huawei-ren-zhengfeis-interview-in-shenzhen-china-question-8"><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>As the most of valuable Chinese Company we
can find in China, We pay special attention to Huawei. At Huawei headquarters
in Shenzhen，Ren Zhengfei spoke passionately for one hundred and fifty minutes
with Chinese media. Valuefinding noted down 62 questions of the interview in
English. we also annotated the answer given by Ren Zhengfei. The following is
question 8.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Q8 Financial Weekly: After the US export control goes into effect, Huawei's suppliers in Japan, Europe, and Taiwan maybe help Huawei a lot. If this export control won’t wok wel , do you think the US government will put pressure on companies like TSMC? Huawei can design chips, but it does not have the capabilities of the entire value chain. The following is question 8.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Ren Zhengfei: If more companies refuse to
succumb to the pressure, then even more will follow. We don't worry too much
about this. After all, this is not happening.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Financial Weekly: Considering Google's recent action to Huawei, users in Europe are very worried that Huawei phones will not be able to use the latest Android in the future. What's your opinion on this? How to deal with it?</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Ren: Google is a good company – a highly responsible company. They are also trying to persuade the US government to solve this problem. We're now discussing viable solutions or relief program for this, and our experts are still working on this. So I can't give you a detailed or completed answer today.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content><author><name>huujuun</name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the most of valuable Chinese Company we can find in China, We pay special attention to Huawei. At Huawei headquarters in Shenzhen，Ren Zhengfei spoke passionately for one hundred and fifty minutes with Chinese media. Valuefinding noted down 62 questions of the interview in English. we also annotated the answer given by Ren Zhengfei. The following is question 8.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Interview with Founder and CEO of Huawei Ren Zhengfei In Shenzhen, China, Question 1</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/founder-and-ceo-of-huawei-ren-zhengfeis-interview-in-shenzhen-china-question-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Interview with Founder and CEO of Huawei Ren Zhengfei In Shenzhen, China, Question 1" /><published>2019-05-28T14:40:00+08:00</published><updated>2019-05-28T14:40:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/founder-and-ceo-of-huawei-ren-zhengfeis-interview-in-shenzhen-china-question-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/founder-and-ceo-of-huawei-ren-zhengfeis-interview-in-shenzhen-china-question-1"><![CDATA[<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>As the most of valuable Chinese Company we can find in China, We pay special attention to Huawei. At Huawei headquarters in Shenzhen，Ren Zhengfei spoke passionately for one hundred and fifty minutes with Chinese media. Valuefinding noted down 62 questions of the interview in English. we also annotated the answer given by Ren Zhengfei.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Q1 from CCTV: First of all, I am a reporter
for live broadcast. You have a military background, you are punctual. I am also
punctual. How time flies! Four months ago, we had an interview in this same
place. At that time, the public all felt that Huawei had hit its lowest point.
Everyone was so concerned about Huawei, and then there are many interviews from
domestic and foreign journalists. We didn't expect today's situation to be more
complicated, or even tougher, than it was four months ago. Just now, another
reporter took out a photo of a bullet-ridden aircraft. I was also given this
same photo. It is a photo of the badly damaged fighter aircraft. I heard that
you like this photo very much.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p>Ren Zhengfei: I early saw this photo on the
site wukong.com, feeling that the photo of aircraft was quite like the
situation of our company. So I sent it to my colleagues. The Carrier BG thought
the aircraft in this photo is similar to its situation and started using it for
communications inside and outside the company. Later, we found that there were
not many major problems with the Carrier BG after analysis, since we have been
getting fully prepared over these past more than ten years. So our current
situation is that we are repairing our "aircraft" during its flight
so that it strive to fly back home.</p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->

<!-- wp:image {"id":15} -->
<figure class="wp-block-image"><img src="http://valuefinding.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/05/p1-1024x768.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-15" /></figure>
<!-- /wp:image -->

<!-- wp:paragraph -->
<p></p>
<!-- /wp:paragraph -->]]></content><author><name>huujuun</name></author><category term="blog" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the most of valuable Chinese Company we can find in China, We pay special attention to Huawei. At Huawei headquarters in Shenzhen，Ren Zhengfei spoke passionately for one hundred and fifty minutes with Chinese media. Valuefinding noted down 62 questions of the interview in English. we also annotated the answer given by Ren Zhengfei.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">12</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/12" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="12" /><published>2019-05-28T02:14:00+08:00</published><updated>2019-05-28T02:14:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/12</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/12"><![CDATA[]]></content><author><name>huujuun</name></author><category term="Menu 1" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry></feed>